

SANTIAGO BENEGAS

VIDEO EDITOR

CONTACT

- **(**+54) 11 6492-5296
- ✓ professionalredscontact@gmail.com
- Buenos Aires, Argentina
- My Portfolio: [Behance Link]

SKILLS

- Problem-solving
- Advanced skills in Adobe Premiere Pro
- Highly skilled in Adobe After Effects
- Proficient in Adobe Photoshop
- Expertise in social media management
- Agile in delivering results
- Expert in editing horizontal and vertical videos, and thumbnails.
- Experienced in Canva and Capcut

LANGUAGES

- English (C1)
- Spanish (Native)

REFERENCE

Sebastián Tobias Cordova Artist. Music Producer

Email: sebastiantobiasc@gmail.com

8

ABOUT ME

I am Santiago Benegas, a professional video editor with over two years of experience specializing in creating eye-catching and impactful content. I focus on engaging animations and compelling storytelling to enhance and support the message behind the content, making it more attractive and memorable.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance, Video Editor

Music Visualizer Editor for independent artists

Video Editor and Thumbnail Designer

October 2023 - Present

Youtube Channel: S3BZS (113K Suscribers)

April 2024 - October 2024

Youtube Channel: Rodricci (149K Suscribers)

As a Video Editor and Thumbnail Designer specializing in music visualizers, I transform static images or cover art into dynamic, rhythm-synchronized visual experiences.

Freelance, Front-end Developer & Web Design

Hooly App (Start Up): December 2022 - September 2023

TangoSwap.cash (Crypto Exchange): August 2022 - January 2023

WenLambo.cash (Crypto): December 2021 - September 2023



EDUCATION

Advanced English Certification (C1)

July 2023

EF SET (English First Standard Education Test) https://www.efset.org/cert/BmchgR

Secondary Education: Escuela Normal Superior N°6 2016 - 2022 Bachelor in Natural Sciences